<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<page skip="no" enable_next="yes" dlink="no" has_graphic="yes" has_popup="yes" has_audio="no" layout="h_txt_img" pg_num="06">

	<nav prev_page="01_00_005.html" next_page="01_00_007.html" />

	<mod_title id="1">Course Introduction and CHK Search Overview</mod_title>
	
	<pg_title>Knowledge Checks</pg_title>
	
	<text_content>
		<paragraph>Throughout each module, you will be given continual practice with specific feedback, through the use of (??)Knowledge Checks(%??)[##link=popup##]. These questions are meant to help you retain the information you are learning so you can apply it in your job.</paragraph> 
		<paragraph>These questions could be in a variety of formats. Selecting the graphics on this page will show you the types of questions you will see in this course.</paragraph>
	</text_content>
	
	<graphic selectable="no">
		<filename>01_00_006.png</filename>
		<alt></alt>
	</graphic>
	
	<prompt>CLICK THE HIGHLIGHTED TEXT AND EACH GRAPHIC TO LEARN MORE. THEN CLICK THE NEXT ARROW TO CONTINUE.</prompt>
	
	<audios autoplay="yes">
	  	<audio>
			<filename>01_00_006_1</filename>
			<cc_text>
				<paragraph></paragraph>
			</cc_text>
	  	</audio>
	</audios>
	
	<popups>
	  <popup id="1" has_image="no">
		  <popTitle>Knowledge Checks</popTitle>
		  <popText>
			  <paragraph>Knowledge Checks are questions that are designed to let you test your understanding and retention of what you've learned. You will be able to read feedback about your answers that will help you understand why particular choices are correct or incorrect.</paragraph>
			  <paragraph>Most knowledge review questions allow two attempts. If you answer incorrectly on your first attempt, you will be prompted to try again. If you answer incorrectly on your second try, the correct response will be provided.</paragraph>
		  </popText>
	  </popup>

	  <popup id="2" has_image="yes">
		  <popTitle>Matching (Drag and Drop)</popTitle>
		  <popText>
			  <paragraph>In this course, drag and drop interactions are used to build a list of items in a category. To complete a drag and drop interaction, you will drag items from the list to the correct answers list. If the item correctly answers the question, the interaction will provide you with the correct feedback. If the item does not answer the question correctly, it will simply return to its place in the list.</paragraph>
		  </popText>
		  
		  <popImg>
			<filename>01_00_006a.png</filename>
			<alt>Selectable graphic of a Drag and Drop interaction labeled Drag and Drop</alt>
		  </popImg>
		</popup>

	  <popup id="3" has_image="yes">
		  <popTitle>Matching (Click Grid)</popTitle>
		  <popText>
			  <paragraph>Below is an example of a click grid, which is a type of matching interaction you will see in this course. To complete a click grid, you will click the blocks in the table. If you want to change your answer, simply click another block in the same row.</paragraph>
		  </popText>
		  
		  <popImg>
			<filename>01_00_006b.png</filename>
			<alt>Selectable graphic of a Click Grid interaction labeled Click Grid.</alt>
		  </popImg>
		</popup>

	  <popup id="4" has_image="yes">
		  <popTitle>Scenario-based Exercise</popTitle>
		  <popText>
			  <paragraph>Scenarios will be used so that you can relate the use of CHK Search to your job-related tasks. This will give you the opportunity to apply concepts covered in the course to real life situations.</paragraph>
		  </popText>
		  
		  <popImg>
			<filename>01_00_006c.png</filename>
			<alt>Selectable graphic of a Scenario-based Exercise interaction labeled Scenario-based Exercise.</alt>
		  </popImg>
		</popup>

	</popups>

</page>