<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<page skip="no" enable_next="yes" dlink="yes" has_graphic="yes" has_popup="no" has_audio="yes" layout="v_txt_img" pg_num="09">

	<nav prev_page="03_00_008.html" next_page="03_00_010.html" />

	<mod_title id="3">Contracts Search</mod_title>
	
	<pg_title>Print Contract Data Sheet</pg_title>
	
	<text_content>
		<paragraph>There may be times when you need to refer to a contract and you’re far from an Internet connected device, or you may just want a copy of the contract details on hand for quick reference.  You can get this readily available copy by printing a contract data sheet.</paragraph>
		<paragraph>The demonstration below describes the steps for printing a contract data sheet. Select Play to view the demonstration.</paragraph>
	</text_content>
	
	<graphic selectable="no" top_position="83">
		<filename>03_00_009a.png</filename>
		<alt>Graphic screenshot of the Show Me interaction, with a Play button overlaid.</alt>
	</graphic>
	
	<prompt>SELECT PLAY TO VIEW THE DEMONSTRATION. THEN CLICK THE NEXT AROW TO CONTINUE.</prompt>
	
	<audios autoplay="yes">
	  	<audio>
			<filename>03_00_009_1</filename>
			<cc_text>
			  <paragraph>There may be times when you need to refer to a contract and you’re far from an Internet connected device, or you may just want a copy of the contract details on hand for quick reference.  You can get this readily available copy by printing a contract data sheet.</paragraph>
			  
			  <paragraph>The demonstration below describes the steps for printing a contract data sheet. Select Play to view the demonstration.</paragraph>
			  
			  <paragraph>In the Data Grid, check any or all the checkboxes next to the Contract Number(s) to select the contract data sheet(s) to print.</paragraph>			  
			  <paragraph>Click the Result Actions dropdown list. The Result Actions dropdown list expands.</paragraph>	
			  		  
			  <paragraph>Select Print Contract Data Sheets.</paragraph>
			  			  
			  <paragraph>A new bowser window opens and a File Download dialog box displays with information about the generated PDF contract data sheet.</paragraph>			  
			  <paragraph>Select Open. Note that at this point you also have the option to save the data sheet to a location on your computer, instead of printing it.</paragraph>			  
			  <paragraph>The document opens in your default PDF viewer.</paragraph>			  
			  <paragraph>In your PDF viewer’s Menu Bar, select File.  From there you can either save the data sheet to a location on your computer, or print out a copy.</paragraph>			  
			</cc_text>
	  	</audio>
	</audios>
	
	<dlink link_type="file">
		<linkTxt>Select this link for a text alternative to the demonstration.</linkTxt>
		<linkTo>03_00_009-p1.pdf</linkTo>
	</dlink>
	
</page>